# Antari Dwijayanti

+6285157734785 | antaridwijayanti@gmail.com | Bali, Indonesia | https://www.antaridwijayanti.com/

# **Summary**

A Web Developer with over 2 years of experience in developing and maintaining websites.using HTML, CSS, Javascript, JQuery, and Laravel. Adept at creating responsive interfaces to enhance user experience. Possessing a keen eye for detail and problem-solving abilities. Eager to learn and apply new technologies, particularly on the front-end side.

#### Skills

- Web Development: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Tailwind, Javascript, JQuery, PHP, Laravel, Codelgniter, React.js, Next.js
- Others: Dart, Flutter, Figma, Adobe XD, GIT

## **Experience**

#### Fullstack Developer (Full time)

July 2022 - Current

## PT. APPKEY, Bali, Indonesia

- Developed three client websites with responsive interface using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, jQuery, and Laravel.
- Maintained the t-bank.jp website and successfully fixed an overloaded datatable issue on the front-end, which contained over 2000 users, within two days.
- Troubleshot and resolved nine bugs on the PT. Sumiati Ekspor Indonesia internal web system, which uses the Codelgniter framework, within nine days, with most of the bugs being on the front-end side.
- Implemented third-party services APIs for client websites, including Square Payment Gateway, Midtrans Payment Gateway, and Google Place API.
- Created APIs for two mobile apps, including a taxi app and a food ordering app, using Laravel.
- Developed the OracleAl mobile app within three months using Flutter after learning the framework for two weeks.

## Freelancer (Self Employed)

May 2024 - Current

• Designed and developed a car rental website with an engaging UI both user and admin sides for balibagusrentcar.com using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, and Laravel. Also implemented SEO best practices to improve search engine ranking and attract potential customers.

#### Web Developer (Internship)

April 2022 - July 2022

#### CV. ARTANA ADHITAMA (KAYANA CREATIVE), Bali, Indonesia

· Designed and developed a waste management system for Ungasan village using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, and Laravel.

## **UI/UX Designer** (Internship)

Aug 2021 - Dec 2021

### PT. IMPACTBYTE TEKNOLOGI EDUKASI, Jakarta, Indonesia (Remote)

· Redesigning CROWDE's website UI to be more user-friendly.

#### Education

Bachelor: Information System - ITB STIKOM Bali July 2022

GPA: 3.84